This position, this timing, this angle, it's perfection.
Wow, you actually pulled it off.
Obviously, I could never be as accurate as Kageyama, but when you see something that cool, you want to try to do it, right?
Man, that's the kind of trust you can only find in twins.
You two are so lucky to have each other, you know that?
Trust. I don't actually trust Sumu that much.
He never listens to anything I say.
Where are you, Samu? You're supposed to wake me up!
I did, and said I had to be in early for class duty.
He never returns anything he borrows. That's my jacket.
Can I wear it?
You can ask to borrow new stuff once you return the other stuff.
I didn't eat it!
Dude, and he's a big, fat liar.
But who needs trust, anyway?
I mean, I know the ball's coming my way.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't care.
It was inside, it was completely brutal
It won't be enough
I free the best half, it's the best house
Thank you.
喜べそうだよな 今をやめない 味わい尽くして笑おう 笑ってやろうぜ
Look at that speed! They're just as fast, if not faster, than Karasuno's first-year duo!
You're really creepy, you know that man?
Stop flattering me, please!
Got it!
Sorry, cover!
The messier their reception, the more likely Kageyama is to try and force a quick attack.
And since we just showed him our quick, I know exactly who he'll be looking for.
Hinata!
You're down!
And Anazaki just utterly destroyed Karasuno's main attack, Phil.
The way they set up that block, it was like they knew the ball would go to Hinata before it got there.
Ginger and not Ginger, settle down! Don't get so worked up!
I'm as calm as I always am.
Oh, right.
The Mia brothers are unstoppable!
These Wonder Twins have been activated!
That number 10 is an excellent score for being so small.
But I would imagine he must be a little bit discouraged to see someone else using his one-of-a-kind moves so easily.
Hmm.
You think so?
Up until now, I don't think anyone believed he could do much without Kageyama.
They have a connection.
And after all, it's not like he'll be able to play with him as a setter for the rest of his career.
So as far as that quick attack is concerned,
Atsumu has proven that there are other setters out there in the world who can make sure Hinata gets the ball.
Might even be a first.
I actually think he may welcome that fact.
The serves he needs are not one-of-a-kind.
Look at that!
I wouldn't call that the face of a discouraged player, would you?
Sorry! Cover!
Your unpredictability is so predictable, Kageyama.
Out!
A blocker got a finger on the ball!
That's a point for Karasuno!
Damn.
Hey, Karai, do you think he...
Oh, yeah.
He could see it.
I'm as calm as I always am.
That wasn't bravado. He wasn't just acting tough.
He was legitimately tossing up the sets he thought were best.
He was just telling me that he doesn't have control over everything that happens after that.
I'd bet anything the old Kageyama would have tightened up immediately and started trying to do everything on his own out there.
Front!
Now it's Karasuno's turn to make some noise on defense.
The Miya Quiz, stopped by first-year Kei Tsukashima.
We really did it!
The biggest threat to the Freak Quick's effectiveness is the blockers getting used to it.
And if any player out there has managed to earn the title of Freak Quick Killer,
it would be either Aeone from Daytech or Inuoka from Nekoma,
who've both stopped our little red vengeance plenty of times.
Or it could be someone who sees the thing several times a day
and has most likely come to hate it with a mad passion.
Like Tsukashima.
Cool.
I've always wanted to stop one of those things.
Huh?
Uh-huh.
Ah!
One touch!
I had never heard of Karasuno before today,
but they've got a pretty solid lineup out there.
Their Quick Attack's sick, their Samurai Dudes of Force,
and their Libero's got skills.
Ah!
What about ball number five?
He's the crazy one?
Come on, leave the poor kid alone.
Ah!
game coach smells trouble hey you're being really helpful out there today
Tsukushima I stopped that last one because it was obvious they were going
to do it but that quick is still going to be plenty of trouble no kidding
ginger yeah I'm leaving one of the twins to you
huh I want you to go back out on that court and be our Inuoka
just every single one of them have to have an arm-breaking serve
whoo Tsukis gonna take off
go up there and get it damn you kagayama
this has got to be higher than anything from Shira Torizawa
Tsukishima is definitely shining on both offense and defense
that one sure was up there come on guys we could at least high five or something
Tsukishima's face says that went well but I'd rather die than admit it
and kagayama says he's glaring at me so I guess I'll glare right back
hang on Inoshida how can you tell that
it hasn't been that long since the youth intensive
so what the hell happened to kagayama since then
all right let's do this
I swear this never gets any easier and it never will
don't screw up
not to mention we're up against guys I've seen on TV and in magazines
hey he's the she snap out of it and listen up
huh the current and Narazaki receivers are high schooler Hitoshi Ginjima
high schooler Osamu Mia and high schooler Michinari Akagi
that's all
I'm not going up against college players or professionals or extraterrestrials
I'm leaving one of the twins to you
I want you to go back out on that court and be our Inuoka
I'm gonna have Hinata stick to Osamu Mia like glue
so if any attack comes from the left or center
we need to make sure there are two other guys ready to block it
yes sir
with a good running start
Hinata's jump gives him one of the best reaches on the team
and he's got quick reflexes
he'll be able to hold his own
that sounds like something a slightly clever monkey could handle
you jealous that I got put in charge of something important Tsukishima
yeah sure
come on my man don't go getting lazy with your comebacks
we got this
huh
Hinata's commit blocking that friggin guy
I did it
and he scores
the little fella just slammed it past the all-star spiker
it was a fluke
and nobody ever expects you to do it again
I knew he could jump
but damn
he just shows up out of nowhere
I didn't expect him to commit block me
me neither
Hinata did it
it worked
yeah
but
that one was basically a surprise attack
this is where he's gonna have to get really persistent
mine
they're not gonna lay their new move to rest just yet
it took great big guts for Asumu to try that same attack again
nice serve
well done
I couldn't get their setter to hit it underhanded
I could have made that one harder to hit
chance ball
the ball is directly over the net
I'm not up against college players or professionals or extraterrestrials
but I can tell
they're not just high schoolers like me
they're guys who've worked much harder and gained more experience than I ever have
me
I don't stand a chance
but
they do
our freak first years
definitely stand a chance
that kid really is springy
but
that's basically all he is
they duked it out over the net and Inanisaki came out on top
oh well
I guess you're more of a pushover than I originally thought
what did he say?
what did you expect?
the other guy just has more experience
I mean he happened to lose that one ball
but if he keeps having to go through his blocks one on one
that's going to be stressful
especially after Hinata was lucky enough to get that first block
Inanisaki has already figured out how to deal with our free quick attack
it's time for you to get lost in a crowd
got it coach
great plan
you forgot about it didn't you?
you were keeping it in the back of your mind
for the beginning of the game at least
then you saw the twins attack and got hung up on proving you're faster
am I wrong?
loosen up kid
that's the second time I've had to tell you
right
that goes for both spikes and blocks
one more time
nice receive
one touch
sorry
it's close to the net
damn it
I put too much power on that one
stop flacking Samu
I wasn't slacking
oh crap
look at me
I'm gonna be the decoy
everybody can see right through your whole act dude
whatever
if I went full strength for every ball
it wouldn't last through the game
if you'd hit the ball
you'd get it over
so push yourself a little
or what
are you scared of that tiny little blocker?
like hell I'm scared
do you mean that?
well yeah
so he's not scared
I guess a more intimidating blocker would be more like
Eone
but date tech is always like
wow
with at least two guys coming after you
one on one
who was the worst blocker to go one on one against?
who was it?
the worst blocker
the worst
who the heck was it?
no
no slacking
I'm not
one on one
the blocker I hated the most was
don't try a cross shot okay?
you can't do it can you?
good play dude
he made me take a line shot
number 10 isn't coming
get lost in the crowd
synchronized attack
yeah
another break point for Karasuno
they have tied it up yet again Phil
Hinata
did you do that on purpose?
yeah I did
I really hated going against that kind of block
huh?
Kasuntai didn't cover your mouth
badass
whatever works
thank you
yeah
you do know that you aren't the one who scored right?
so?
I am no longer the man who was only good at offense
uh
hey wait
I'm talking to you Kageyama
oh man I'm starting to get kind of hungry
bro
Karasuno is doing much better than I thought they would
this game was billed as a bunch of newcomers playing against a superior team
but it's actually a Narazaki that's been struggling to deal with Karasuno
at least up to this point
Coach Yukai's grandson sees it too
he's making sure his guys are constantly evolving
throwing a range of new attacks at the other team
but if they let up for a second they could get overwhelmed
it may be that the real battle begins once they've used up all their little tricks
when number 10 doesn't run up in front do you think it's a planned thing?
or do you think it was a coincidence?
if you think back to the Shiratorizawa game
a play looking something like that happened there too
hey what did I tell you?
if you get distracted by their number 10
then you're falling right into their trap
sometimes you adapt to your opponent
sometimes you stand your ground
know the difference guys
and remember
re-blocking works much better in the second half of the game
yes sir
damn
Alan
three blockers
yes
did that spike just go all the way over our triple block?
hey Asahi
you're welcome to start doing that anytime you want
yeah I could never hit over like that
side out serve
damn it
what a monster serve
all they could do was try to put the ball back in the air
left
Asahi
that was kind of okay
I actually pulled off an okay set
lucky bastard
three blockers
crap
how in the world did that happen?
oh
all right
sorry about that
they got this far and they're still trying new things
damn bird brains
my precious chance to play in the back row
all right
yes
look at him at the
he's even more hyped about serving than usual
yeah and his serve sucks too
maybe he's more excited about playing for receives than serves
hmm
oh
yeah
huh
Tadashi's pinch serving for him
right
now go get him
you better score ten points
why are there tears in your eyes man
go on
you've got this
I can't really explain why
but I feel like we can totally beat these guys
one thing at a time just like always
the way I walk
the way I touch the ball
hmm
my target is their ace
ideally I can bring him to his knees
now I reset
just like in the Tsubaki Haro match
what
I could see it during warm-ups
calm down
just find something else
something
nice
will the manager for Onida girls academy team
please deliver your entry sheet to the main office
concentrate
you did just fine yesterday
reset
just reset
Tadashi
remember the bag
take it
oh
sorry about that everyone
yeah
Tadashi that's my boy
he did so good
it's so ready
seriously
I can serve like that
one more time
little sorry
yeah
no
oh
yeah
Thank you.
Next time, Broken Heart.